everywebsite.net 2011-01-14

# Every Website Directory - Privacy Policy

**WHO ARE WE**  
In this privacy policy references to 'we', 'us' and 'our' are to www.everywebsite.net Owner. References to 'our Website' or 'the Website' are to www.everywebsite.net.

 **WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW**  
The information we collect via the Website may include:   
1\. Any personal details you knowingly provide us with through forms and our email, such as name, address, telephone number etc.  
2\. Please note that all our payments are processed by PayPal. www.everywebsite.net will never request any debit or credit card details or any bank account information.  
3\. Your preferences and use of email updates, recorded by emails we send you (if you select to receive email updates on products and offers).  
4\. Your IP Address, this is a string of numbers unique to your computer that is recorded by our web server when you request any page or component on the Website. This information is used to monitor your usage of the Website.  
5\. Data recorded by the Website which allows us to recognise you and your preferred settings, this saves you from re-entering information on return visits to the site. Such data is recorded locally on you computer through the use of cookies. Most browsers can be programmed to reject, or warn you before downloading cookies, information regarding this may be found in your browsers 'help' facility.

 **WHAT WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION**  
Any personal information we collect from this website will be used in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and other applicable laws. The details we collect will be used:  
1\. To process your order, to provide after sales service (we may pass your details to another organisation to supply/deliver products or services you have purchased and/or to provide after-sales service);  
2\. In certain cases we may use your email address to send you information on our other products and services. By submitting a listing and clicking the link in the verification email, you consent to recieve such mailings occasionally.  
3\. We may need to pass the information we collect to other companies for administrative purposes. We may use third parties to carry out certain activities, such as processing and sorting data, monitoring how customers use the Website and issuing our e-mails for us. Third parties will not be allowed to use your personal information for their own purposes.

 **YOUR RIGHTS**  
You have the right to request a copy of any information that we currently hold about you. In order to receive such information please send your contact details including address to us via the following form: [Contact Us](http://www.everywebsite.net/contact.php) (Please note that a payment of £12 will be required to cover administration expenses)

 **OTHER WEBSITES**  
This privacy policy only covers this website. Any other websites which may be linked to by our website are subject to their own policy, which may differ from ours.

© Copyright 2006-2009, [Every Website Directory](http://www.everywebsite.net/ "Every Website Directory"), All rights Reserved. [Privacy](http://www.everywebsite.net/privacy.php "Privacy Policy") & [Terms](http://www.everywebsite.net/terms.php "Terms of use"). Powered by [phpLD](http://www.phplinkdirectory.com/ "PHP Link Directory").
